<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lichen Guide</string>
    <string name="titleText">Lichen Guide</string>
    <string name="EEON_prompt">Select Plot</string>
        <string name="LichenList">Lichen Index</string>
    
    
    
    <string-array name="optionsMenu">
    	<item>Glossary of Terms</item>
		<item>About Lichen Guide</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="start_page_options">
    <item>Key to Genera</item>
    <item>Species Index</item>
    <item>Glossary</item>
    <item>About</item>
    
    
    </string-array>
    

    
    <string-array name="couplet1">   
     
    <item>1A - Thallus foliose or fruticose.  On branches or trunks of conifers and hardwoods.</item>   
    <item>1B - Fruit-body resembling a typical cap and stem mushroom</item>
    <item>1C - Podetiate and arising from light green primary squamules</item> 
    <item>1D - Thallus fruticose, erect and abundantly branched, generally with small spherical protrusions 
    at ends of branches, color light tan/cream to orangish brown.</item>
    
    </string-array>
    
    
    
    <string-array name="couplet2">   
     
    <item>2A - Thallus foliose, with distinctly different upper and lower surfaces.  Epiphytic on tree branches, 
    			trunks or stumps, or on the ground, often among moss.  Color various.</item>   
    <item>2B - Thallus fruticose, branches generally round to flattened. Branches either solid or hollow.  
    			Epiphytic on tree branches and trunks.  Color various.</item>
    
    </string-array>
    
    

    <string-array name="couplet3">   
     
    <item>3A - Underside of thallus generally without noticeable rhizines.  Other thallus characteristics various.</item>   
    <item>3B - Underside of thallus with few to abundant rhizines.  Other thallus characteristics various.</item>
    
    </string-array>
 
 
    <string-array name="couplet4">   
     
    <item>4A - Thallus usually large, surface wrinkled/ridged; bright green to dull grey/green when fresh.  
    		Circular soralia often abundant on surface ridges and margins.  Underside white, tan/cream to brown and ridged.  
    		Apothecia uncommon.</item>   
    <item>4B - Lobes hollow, interior various.  Color ranges from white to light grey/green to green. Sorediate or not.</item>
    
    </string-array> 

    
    <string-array name="couplet5">   
     
    <item>5A - Thallus lobes small, appressed to substrate, with noticeable holes in top surface.  
    		Soredia abundant in roughly hood shaped to torn/upturned soralia on lobe tips.  Color white to light green.  
    		Often appearing to grow out from a central point, on branches and tree trunks.            </item>   
    <item>5B - Lobes of various sizes and lengths, sub-erect, erect to appressed.  Lobe interiors various, ranging from white to brown.  
    		Several species with holes in lobe branch axils.  Soredia present or not.  Common and abundant in coniferous areas.</item>
    
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="couplet6">
    <item>6A - Thallus with marginal cilia.  Cilia variously colored, long or short. </item>
    <item>6B - Thallus without cilia. </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet7">
    <item>7A - Thallus small, lobes narrow, usually less than 1mm wide. Color white to pale grey.  
    		Rhizines usually not abundant.  Soredia present at lobe tips in irregular/lip shaped soralia. </item>
    <item>7B - Thallus much larger than above.  Color white to light green/grey.  
    		Abundant to sparse black marginal cilia.  Soredia present in rounded soralia at lobe tips.   </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet8">
    <item>8A - Thallus some shade olive green/brown to green.  Rhizines few to lacking.  Isidia, pycnidia, or soredia present.  
    		Most commonly on branches.  Growing erect to suberect or appressed. </item>
    <item>8B - Thallus some other color.  If brown to dark gray, then with distinct, prominent rhizines and veins on underside. </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet9">
    <item>9A - Abundant black, mostly marginal, though sometimes laminal pycnidia; marginal apothecia common OR margins 
    	wihout pycndia but with marginal soralia.     </item>
    	
    <item>9B - Growing appressed to subsrate, lacking soredia.  Isidia mostly laminal, finger-like, easily breaking off.  </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet10">
    <item>10A - Thallus color various, but ranges from brown to dark grey to gray/green.  
    		Underside of thallus with both prominent rhizines and veins. Rhizines tomentose to smooth or tufted.   
    		Apothecia, if present, usually orange and protruding from lobe tips. Lobes often broad and growing in large clumps.  
    		Almost always growing embedded in moss either on the ground or epiphytically on trees, most often hardwoods.   </item>
    		
    <item>10B - Upper surface usually light grey/green.  Underside with sparse to lacking rhizines and a combination of 
    		some shade of black, brown or white OR underside with abundant, small black rhizines with various branching patterns. </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet11">
    <item>11A - Lobes broad to narrow, often ragged looking, with few to sparse rhizines.  
    		Isidia or soredia usually present, often abundant on margins.  Underside usually some combination of black, brown or white. </item>
    <item>11B - Lobes generally narrow, thallus small, with abundant black rhizines. </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet12">
    <item>12A - Soredia on rounded lobe tips, rhizines branching dichotomously.  Isidia lacking.     </item>
    <item>12B - Soredia or isidia present, either laminally or on margins.  Rhizines branching squarrosely or otherwise.  
    		Very common.     </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet13">
    <item>13A - Tufted or pendulous on tree branches or trunks.  Has a distinct, 
    		elastic-like internal cord running through the branches.  Medulla cotton-like, thin to dense around the cord.  </item>
    <item>13B - Thallus without an internal cord.  Color various. </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet14">
    <item>14A - Thallus branches mostly flattened, dichotomous.  Usually tufted but some specimens can appear pendulous. </item>
    <item>14B - Thallus round, thin, string/thread-like, often without an obvious point of attachment to the substrate.  
    		Color ranges from light greenish/yellow to dark brown, grey.  Often pendulous from conifer branches. </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet15">
    <item>15A - Ventral surface light green to green/gray, while underside of branch is much lighter, often white.		 </item>
    <item>15B -  Thallus uniformly light green/yellow.  Often with round/elliptical marginal or laminal soralia. 
    			Some species with abundant apothecia.	   </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet16">
    <item>16A - Color light green.  Apothecia lecanorine, the disc light brown.  Branches with prominent, elongate, white pseudocyphallae. </item>
    <item>16B - Color grey to brown.  String/thread like.  Soredia and isidia present or not.		 </item>
    
    </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="couplet17">
    <item>17A - Fruit body a mushroom, pale tan/orange to cream with decurrent gills, growing from dark green primary thallus.  
    	Common on rotting wood and stumps.	 </item>
    
    <item>17B - Not like above. </item>
    </string-array>
    
    
        <string-array name="couplet18">
    <item>18A - Thallus erect and abundantly branched with spherical apothecia at branch ends.  
    Apothecia bursting, revealing a black interior.  Most common on hardwood branches and trunks.    </item>
    <item>18B - Distinct podetia (cup-shaped or otherwise) arising from small, leafy squamules.  
    Apothecia color various, usually ranging from brown to red, or absent.  Common on conifer trunks, but also on stumps, 
    uncommon on branches.   </item>
    
    </string-array>
    

    

    
    
    
    
</resources>
